<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>HUGE Magazine</title><description>Daily startup features, powered by Product Hunt. We write features, not press releases.</description><link>https://hugemagazine.com/</link><language>en-us</language><item><title>Claude Code Has a Memory Problem. Claudebin Is at Least Trying to Fix It.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/claudebin/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/claudebin/</guid><description>Your AI coding sessions vanish into terminal logs nobody can read — one open-source tool thinks that&apos;s worth solving.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arc Left a Hole in the Market. Someone Built a Sidebar to Fill It.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/arcmark/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/arcmark/</guid><description>When Arc pulled back, it didn&apos;t just leave users without a browser — it left them without a workflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Apple Watch Has Always Been a Closed Garden. Merge Is Digging a Tunnel Under the Fence.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/merge-b1196c9f-92ff-4d43-b239-0ce4da5a9339/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/merge-b1196c9f-92ff-4d43-b239-0ce4da5a9339/</guid><description>Apple Watch hardware is genuinely good — it&apos;s the software leash that forces you to buy the whole ecosystem. Merge is betting you&apos;re tired of that deal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Prompt That Finds Your Next 1,000 Customers</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/origami-chat/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/origami-chat/</guid><description>Lead generation has always been a numbers game dressed up as a skill. Origami.chat thinks one prompt should do the heavy lifting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Claude Without the Setup: Clawi Bets the Cloud Is Enough</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawi-ai/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawi-ai/</guid><description>Running your own AI assistant used to mean managing servers. Clawi wants to make that someone else&apos;s problem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stop Prompting. Start Talking. Reloop Wants to Rethink the AI Ad Workflow</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/reloop/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/reloop/</guid><description>Every AI video tool promises to kill the agency. Reloop&apos;s angle is different: it promises to kill the prompt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monologue Wants to Be the Last Stop Between Your Mouth and Every App You Type In</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/monologue-for-ios/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/monologue-for-ios/</guid><description>Voice-to-text has been around long enough to feel boring — Monologue is betting the problem was never transcription, it was everything that came after.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nobody Likes Filling Out Forms. This Open-Source Project Wants You to Talk Instead.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/kollect-voice-agent/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/kollect-voice-agent/</guid><description>Kollect replaces the survey grid with a voice conversation — and it&apos;s self-hostable, MIT-licensed, and already making a case for why forms are a UX relic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moda</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/moda-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/moda-2/</guid><description>Finally, AI designs you can edit</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Built AI Agents. Now You Have No Idea What They&apos;re Doing.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawmetry-for-openclaw/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawmetry-for-openclaw/</guid><description>ClawMetry is a free observability dashboard for OpenClaw agents — and the fact that it needs to exist says a lot about where AI tooling actually is right now.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SPECTRE Wants to Be the Last Workflow Standing in the AI Coding Agent Wars</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/spectre-5/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/spectre-5/</guid><description>When every AI coding tool is racing to be smarter, one open-source project is betting the real problem is that nobody taught these agents how to think in steps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Layers Wants to Be the Marketing Brain Your App Never Had</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/layers-ed518cb6-abce-403d-ac51-8749d88bf0cc/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/layers-ed518cb6-abce-403d-ac51-8749d88bf0cc/</guid><description>A new AI marketing platform claims it can read your code and run your growth strategy — which is either exactly what solo founders need or a very confident promise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MiniMax Wants to Make Long-Running AI Agents Economically Boring</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/minimax-m2-5/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/minimax-m2-5/</guid><description>An open-source model from a Chinese AI lab just posted benchmark numbers that should make Anthropic at least glance up from whatever they&apos;re doing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Think You Know Your Web Traffic. You Don&apos;t.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/agent-monitor/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/agent-monitor/</guid><description>An SEO agency got tired of GA4 lying to their face, so they built the thing that actually tells you who&apos;s crawling your site — and it turns out, it&apos;s mostly not humans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Base44 Wants to Be the Backend You Never Have to Think About Again</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/base44-backend-platform/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/base44-backend-platform/</guid><description>AI coding agents are getting good at writing code — turns out the part that keeps breaking is everything underneath it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NVIDIA Just Broke the One Rule of Full-Duplex Voice AI</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/nvidia-personaplex/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/nvidia-personaplex/</guid><description>Every natural-sounding voice AI made you take what you got — NVIDIA&apos;s PersonaPlex is a serious attempt to change that.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One API to Rule Your Claws: Chowder Bets the AI Agent Deployment Problem Is Bigger Than It Looks</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/chowder-dev/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/chowder-dev/</guid><description>Building an AI agent is the easy part now — deploying it somewhere useful, connecting it to your users, and keeping it running is where things quietly fall apart.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Guy, One Prompt, and a $50K ARR Argument Against the Entire Stock Footage Industry</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/lunair/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/lunair/</guid><description>Lunair hit #1 on Product Hunt by promising what every solo founder quietly dreads doing themselves: making a video that doesn&apos;t look terrible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Six Dollars and a Keyboard Shortcut: The Anti-Subscription Case for Prompt Management</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/prompt-library/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/prompt-library/</guid><description>Everyone has a notes app graveyard of prompts they&apos;ll &apos;definitely reuse.&apos; Prompt Library is betting $6.35 that there&apos;s a cleaner way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Formaly</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/formaly/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/formaly/</guid><description>Forms that feel like conversations</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cline Wants to Be the AI Agent That Actually Lives in Your Pipeline</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/cline-cli-2-0/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/cline-cli-2-0/</guid><description>The terminal is having a moment, and Cline CLI 2.0 is betting it can be the thing that makes AI coding agents actually useful in production — not just in the IDE.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your AI Keeps Living in a Tab. TexTab Wants to Put It in Your Fingers.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/textab/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/textab/</guid><description>A Mac utility that binds AI actions to keyboard shortcuts is either the missing layer the power-user crowd has been waiting for, or another tool that sounds great until you realize you have to set it up yourself.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nobody Reads the Terms. Termsy Is Betting That&apos;s Actually a Product Opportunity.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/termsy/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/termsy/</guid><description>A Chrome extension that summarizes the legal fine print you&apos;ve been clicking through for twenty years — sensible idea, crowded-ish space, 105 users so far.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One API to Rule Them All — And a Money-Back Clause If It Doesn&apos;t</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/zenmux-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/zenmux-2/</guid><description>ZenMux wants to be the last LLM integration you ever write — and it&apos;s willing to pay you if it isn&apos;t.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI Built a Fast Coding Model. The Interesting Part Is the Hardware Deal Behind It.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/gpt-5-3-codex-spark/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/gpt-5-3-codex-spark/</guid><description>Codex-Spark hits 1,000+ tokens per second by running on Cerebras chips — and that partnership might matter more than the model itself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenClaw for People Who Don&apos;t Want to Touch a Terminal</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/atomic-bot/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/atomic-bot/</guid><description>Atomic Bot wraps a genuinely powerful AI agent framework in a one-click macOS app — which is either brilliant product thinking or an elaborate wrapper in search of a moat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starnus Wants to Be Your Entire Outbound Sales Team. That&apos;s Either the Pitch or the Problem.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/starnus/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/starnus/</guid><description>Another AI sales tool launched on Product Hunt this week — except this one hit #1 daily with 558 votes, which means it&apos;s worth actually looking at.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Video Has a Consistency Problem. Visla Is Betting a Storyboard Layer Fixes It.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/visla-ai-director-mode/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/visla-ai-director-mode/</guid><description>Everyone can generate a video clip now. Almost nobody can generate ten of them that look like they belong together.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cube Wants to Be the Semantic Layer AI Actually Uses — Not Just the One You Deploy and Forget</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/cube-7/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/cube-7/</guid><description>Every AI analytics tool promises to answer your data questions. Cube says the others are lying to you — and it has 19,000 GitHub stars worth of infrastructure to make that case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Revo Wants to Answer Your Emails For You. The Bar Is Low Enough That It Might Actually Work.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/revo-ai-email-assistant/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/revo-ai-email-assistant/</guid><description>Everyone is building AI email tools. Revo is betting that connecting your inbox to everything else you already use is the part everyone else forgot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Subscriptions Are Bleeding You Out. This Calendar App Wants to Staunch the Wound.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/subscription-day-for-ios/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/subscription-day-for-ios/</guid><description>Subscription Day² just landed on iOS with 307 upvotes and a calendar-first take on a problem everyone has but nobody loves solving.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doraverse Wants to Be the Meeting Layer for Companies That Actually Span Multiple Countries</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/doraverse-s-all-in-one-ai-for-meetings/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/doraverse-s-all-in-one-ai-for-meetings/</guid><description>Multilingual meeting AI is a real problem with real incumbents — the question is whether Doraverse has found a wedge or just a feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spawned Wants to Be Product Hunt, Lovable, and Pump.fun at Once — Which, Look</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/spawned/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/spawned/</guid><description>An AI builder that also launches your product to a discovery feed and optionally staples a Solana token to it is either the cleverest product thesis of 2025 or a three-way stretch that snaps under pressure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Form Was Always in the Wrong Place</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/video-forms/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/video-forms/</guid><description>Embedding questions directly into the video timeline sounds obvious in retrospect — which is either a good sign or a warning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tech Stack Is the Tell: PredictLeads Wants to Make Technographics Actually Useful</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/predictleads-technographics-dataset/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/predictleads-technographics-dataset/</guid><description>Knowing what software a company runs is only valuable if the data is fresh, sourced, and queryable — which is exactly what most technographics providers have historically failed to deliver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>837 Votes and a Chrome Extension: SuperX Is Betting X Creators Will Pay for Better Data</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/superx/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/superx/</guid><description>The social media management market is heading toward $164 billion by 2034 — and a Nashville-founded X toolkit just landed #1 on Product Hunt to make its case for a slice of it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Leaderboard for Startup Revenue Growth Sounds Simple. That&apos;s Either Its Genius or Its Problem.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/unicorne/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/unicorne/</guid><description>Unicorne shows you the 20 fastest-growing startups in real time, with verified revenue data — which is either the most useful dashboard you didn&apos;t know you needed, or a beautifully designed distraction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your AI Agent Has a Brain. ClawdTalk Wants to Give It a Phone Number.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawdtalk/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/clawdtalk/</guid><description>Telnyx just shipped a voice layer for Clawdbot — and the actual question is whether talking to your agent beats typing at it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LinkedIn Is Eating the Cold Email Playbook, and Extrovert Is Betting Everything on It</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/extrovert-6/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/extrovert-6/</guid><description>Everyone knows spray-and-pray outreach is dead. Fewer people have a credible alternative. Extrovert thinks the answer is commenting.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sway Thinks You Talk Too Much — In the Best Possible Way</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/sway-15/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/sway-15/</guid><description>Voice-to-structure apps are a crowded bet, but Sway&apos;s refusal to be a transcription tool might be the only interesting thing about the category right now.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your AI Agent Deserves a Body — Someone Made It a Crab Shell</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/openclaw-mac-mini-m4-enclosure/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/openclaw-mac-mini-m4-enclosure/</guid><description>The Mac mini M4 became the accidental hardware of the agentic AI moment, and now someone made it a cute crustacean costume.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One CLI to Rule Them All (If You Have 44 AI Agents, Which, Look)</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/skillkit-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/skillkit-2/</guid><description>Skillkit wants to be npm for AI agent skills — and the fragmentation problem it&apos;s solving is very real, even if the solution raises some questions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PinMe Wants You to Deploy a Website Before You Even Remember to Make an Account</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/pinme-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/pinme-2/</guid><description>Zero config, zero login, zero patience required — PinMe is betting that the hardest part of shipping a frontend is everything that comes before the actual shipping.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LIAM Wants to Be the Assistant You Actually Had in Mind When You First Opened Gmail</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/liam/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/liam/</guid><description>Another AI email tool, yes — but the design decision to live inside your existing inbox instead of replacing it might be the only one that matters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your AI Debugger Is Flying Blind. BetterBugs MCP Wants to Give It Eyes.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/betterbugs-mcp-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/betterbugs-mcp-2/</guid><description>Vibe coding is great until your AI assistant stares at a stack trace like a golden retriever watching TV.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Onboarding Flow Is a Graveyard. Obi Thinks Voice AI Can Fix That.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/obi-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/obi-3/</guid><description>A voice AI agent that runs 1:1 onboarding calls sounds like a fever dream from a sales deck — but the underlying problem it&apos;s solving is very real.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI&apos;s New Codex Helped Build Itself. That&apos;s Either Impressive or a Warning Label.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/gpt-5-3-codex/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/gpt-5-3-codex/</guid><description>GPT-5.3-Codex can steer itself through long-running computer tasks, beat the current benchmarks, and — according to OpenAI — debug its own training runs. The question isn&apos;t whether that&apos;s interesting. It is.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vercel Wants to Own the Whole Stack, Not Just the Edge</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/the-new-v0/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/the-new-v0/</guid><description>v0 was already useful; now Vercel wants to know if &apos;useful&apos; can become &apos;indispensable&apos; before the enterprise window closes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Webflow Wants to Skip the Blank Canvas Problem — With a Prompt</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/webflow-ai-site-builder/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/webflow-ai-site-builder/</guid><description>The no-code giant just shipped an AI site builder that goes from prompt to multi-page production site, and the real question isn&apos;t whether it works — it&apos;s whether Webflow&apos;s existing users actually want this.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GitHub Stops Picking Sides in the AI Coding War</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/github-agent-hq/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/github-agent-hq/</guid><description>Rather than bet on one model winning, GitHub is building the platform where all of them compete — and that might be the shrewdest move in developer tools right now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bunny.net Wants to Be Your Whole Stack — Starting With the Database</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/bunny-database/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/bunny-database/</guid><description>SQLite for the web is a solved problem with about five solutions. Bunny Database is betting its CDN roots make it the one that actually sticks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Spreadsheet Is Not a Database — Sheetful Wants You to Pretend Anyway</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/sheetful-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/sheetful-2/</guid><description>Turning Google Sheets into a REST API isn&apos;t a new idea, but Sheetful is betting there&apos;s still a real market for doing it cleanly and for free.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Code Review That Actually Read the Room (and Your Slack History)</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/unblocked-code-review/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/unblocked-code-review/</guid><description>Everyone&apos;s shipping AI code review tools — Unblocked&apos;s bet is that context is the whole game.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Helply Bets Its Business Model on a Number: 65%</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/helply/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/helply/</guid><description>When your entire pitch is a guarantee, the product better work — and the definition of &apos;work&apos; matters enormously.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI Wants to Be Your Engineering Manager Now</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/codex-by-openai-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/codex-by-openai-3/</guid><description>Codex isn&apos;t really a coding tool anymore — it&apos;s a staffing layer, and that&apos;s either exciting or terrifying depending on how many engineers you employ.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Screen Recordings Are Rotting in a Folder Somewhere — Trupeer Wants to Fix That</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/ai-doc-writer-by-trupeer/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/ai-doc-writer-by-trupeer/</guid><description>Documentation is the work everyone agrees matters and nobody wants to do — Trupeer is betting that vision-based AI can close that gap.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ellie Lives in Slack So You Don&apos;t Have to Live in Jira</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/ask-ellie/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/ask-ellie/</guid><description>Ask Ellie wants to be the engineering team&apos;s single source of truth — and it&apos;s betting that source of truth should live in a chat box.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenClaw for Humans: EasyClaw Bets the Hard Part Was Always the Setup</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/easyclaw/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/easyclaw/</guid><description>Everyone wants an AI agent that texts them back on WhatsApp. Almost nobody wants to spend a weekend debugging Python environments to get there.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Happens When You Give AI Agents a Twitter Account and Walk Away</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/moltweet/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/moltweet/</guid><description>Moltweet is a social network where the users aren&apos;t human — and that&apos;s either a fascinating research window or a very elaborate screensaver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>117x Faster and Free: The Android Video Compressor That Has No Business Being This Good</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/compressor-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/compressor-4/</guid><description>The Play Store&apos;s video compressor category is a swamp of ads and paywalls — and one open-source Kotlin project just walked in and made everyone look slow.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Resume Is a Lossy Format. This Startup Wants to Fix the Compression.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/projects-yard-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/projects-yard-2/</guid><description>The job market is soft, ATS systems are broken, and a Carnegie Mellon-connected team thinks structured project portfolios are the answer — at least for tech candidates who can actually show their work.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Voice Is Already Doing the Work. Superscribe Wants to Credit It.</title><link>https://hugemagazine.com/feature/superscribe-io/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://hugemagazine.com/feature/superscribe-io/</guid><description>A macOS menu bar app that turns dictation into a timesheet sounds almost too obvious — which is exactly why it&apos;s interesting.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>